#### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

PERSONAL DETAILS

NAME Becky Kanorio Kirai

DATE OF BIRTH 18/02/1986

EMAIL kiraibecky@gmail.com

CELL 0724 886 5960

I.D.NO. 24699712

GENDER Female

MARITAL STATUS Married

RELIGION Christian

LANGUAGES Fluent English, Swahili and Kimeru

CURRENT LOCATION Embakasi, Nairobi

## PERSONAL PROFILE

As a Diploma holder in Catering and Accommodation Management from Technical University of Kenya (Formerly Kenya Polytechnic) as well as over 5 years experience in hospitality industry, am ready to take on new responsibilities further my professional career.

My key strengths include strong analytical and logical skills, an eye for detail, communication and interpersonal skills. I enjoy working in a team and help others progress, At the same time I work well independently. As a highly motivated and driven individual I strive on taking up challenges.

JOB EXPERIENCE

NOV 2017 TO DATE: KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN(KFC)

POSITION HELD: ASSISTANT RESTAURANT MANAGER

Duties;

In charge of the restaurant in the absence of the Restaurant General Manager.

Compiling payrolls.

In charge of trainings and customer service.

Controlling labor cost.

Dealing with customer complains

Incharge of weekly orders.

FEB 2017 TO NOV 2017 : KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN(KFC)PTION HELD: SHIFT SUPERVISOR

Duties

Balancing/accounting of restaurant daily stock

Leading a shift.

Ensuring costumers are given 100% services with a YES attittude.

Compiling daily reports.

Giving tasks to team members and following up.

Giving daily projections.

In charge of marketing.

NOV 2015-TO FEB 2017: KENTUCKY FRIED CHICKEN (KFC KENYA FRANCHISE)

POSITION HELD: ALLSTAR TEAM MEMBER.

**Duties** 

Buddy trainer; training newly employed team members

Cashiering and daily banking

Food production; marinating, breading, racking and cooking chickens

Expeditor; burger and twister production.

In charge of customer service

FEB 2012- MAY 2015: KFRYS TASTY FOOD

POSITION HELD: CASHIER/ SUPERVISOR

**Duties** 

Purchasing and managing restaurants supplies and consumables

In time balancing daily ledger accounts and reconciliations

Managing daily operations

Training existing and newly employed staff

Marketing and promoting restaurant products

2010- JAN 2012: EVENTS PLANNING AND CATERING SERVICES (SELF)

POSITION HELD: PLANNING AGENT

**Duties** 

Wedding planning and costing

Venue-floral decorations

Meal preparation/catering

MAY2009 - JULY 2009: NAIROBI SAFARI CLUB

POSITION HELD: INTERN

Areas covered

House keeping

Laundry

Food and beverage service

Food and beverage kitchen

MAY 2008- AUG 2008: YOUNG WOMEN CHRISTIAN ASSOCIATION OK KENYA (YWCA)

POSITION HELD: INTERN

**Areas Covered** 

Production area

Service area

Reception

Housekeeping

PROFESSIONAL TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT

Completed Star2000 training, kfc.

Certified Buddy trainer, kfc.

Certified shift supervisor, kfc.

Certified assistant restaurant manager, kfc.

### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

2007-2010: KENYA POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY COLLEGE (Currently Technical university of Kenya)

Award: DIPLOMA IN CATERING AND ACCOMODATION MANAGEMENT

2001-2004: MACCI GIRLS SECONDARY SCHOOL

Award; Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education, KNEC

1990-2000: ST THERESA BOARDING PRIMARY SCHOOL

Award: Kenya Certificate of Primary Education, KNEC

## TECHNICAL/OTHERS

Computer literate i.e. Ms oe word, outlook, access, power point and internet

First aid training with Kenya Red Cross.

Fire marshal training with Trojan Fire Protection Specialists.

**INTERESTS/HOBBIES** 

Trying new recipes

Reading hospitality journals.

Travelling

# **REFEREES**

**Evans Masinde** 

Restaurant General Manager, KFC

CELL: 0725794938

Pauline Mbogo

Kfrys restaurant

Tel: 0722 303 105

Margaret Wambui Rua

Tel: 0727412965